milliondollarjourney.com 2017-08-04

# Disclaimer/Privacy | Million Dollar Journey

### Disclaimer

* * *

The articles posted on this site are the opinion of the author and is not even close to professional financial advice. Please consult a financial professional before using any information offered on Million Dollar Journey.

### Affiliate Links

* * *

Please note that some links to merchants mentioned within this blog might be using an affiliate link. Using an affiliate link means that, at zero cost to you, I might earn a commission if you buy something through that affiliate link. That said, I never recommend anything I don’t personally use and find to be valuable.

### Privacy Policy

* * *

We respect your privacy.  User data submitted on **[MillionDollarJourney.com](http://www.milliondollarjourney.com//)** will never be given/sold to third parties. E-mail addresses submitted in the comments section will never be involuntarily displayed.

If you chose to receive e-mail updates, you can unsubscribe at any time by following the “unsubscribe” link at the bottom of the e-mail received.

The privacy of our visitors is important to us. We recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you visit Million Dollar Journey, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

### Log Files

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

### Cookies and Web Beacons

We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums.

* Google’s use of the DART cookie  
* Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

We also use third party advertisements on Million Dollar Journey to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies, DART cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. Use of cookies is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites). The use of DART cookies enables advertisers such as Google Adsense to serve ads based on your visit and your visits to other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

We use some third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click her **e.** ](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)

That’s all for now! [**Contact me**](http://www.milliondollarjourney.com/contact-me/) if you have any questions.
